# Wahyu Nor Romadon

Pasuruan, East Java 67181 | www.linkedin.com/in/wahyunorromadon/ | +62 85852568177 | wbedodo@gmail.com

#### **ABOUT ME**

I am a final year student majoring in mathematics education. I often participate in internship activities, showing that I am a lifelong learner. I have experience as a content creator on Instagram, showing that I am a person who is creative and likes to share. I have a great interest in the world of education and am ready to develop my contribution in this field

# **EXPERIENCES**

# SMP Negeri 1 Grati

Mathematics Teacher Assistant

(November 2022 - December 2022)

- Assist math teachers in preparing learning materials and correcting assignments.
- Explaining the subject matter to students who have difficulty understanding it.
- Provide guidance to students in working on math problems.

## PT Zenius Education

Machine Learning Internship Program

(February 2022 - July 2022)

- Study data science especially machine learning using jupyter notebook
- Learn excel data processing and programming languages such as python and MySql
- Solve various problems with the team by using machine learning in the corporate

## Kementrian Sosial Republik Indonesia

Pejuang Muda Internship Program

(October 2021 - December 2021)

- Actively involved in helping social and humanitarian activities organized by the Ministry of Social Affairs of the Republic of Indonesia
- Work together as a team in identifying social problems in the surrounding area and planning and implementing social work programs aimed at solving these problems

# **EDUCATION**

# STKIP Al Hikmah Surabaya

**Bachelors** Mathematics Education Department

(August 2019 - May 2023)

GPA 3.3

- A college who has completed the tahfidz Al-Qur'an 5 juz program
- Head of Al Hikmah Student Cooperative Organization (2021-2022)
- Badan Eksekutif Mahasiswa (BEM) public relations division

# **PROJECTS**

# Blog www.semestabelajar.com

(December 2022 - January 2023)

- Personal project to share knowledge with others
- Created using the blogspot platform with a domain that has been changed

#### Portofolio Website

https://wahyunor.github.io/portfolio-wahyunor/

(January 2022 - May 2022)

- · Create a personal portfolio with html and css using the visual studio code application
- · Personal branding website portfolio

## **SKILLS**

Social Media Management (Experience), Copywriting (Experience), Microsoft Office (Expert), Photo & Video Editing (Experience).

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

**Supply Chain Logistic** 

April 2023

Rutgers the State University of New Jersey

Learn about supply chain logistics in global manufacturing companies

National Intensif Class of Public Speaking

September 2022

BOTA Edukasi Indonesia

Study together to deepen the knowledge of public speaking to be used in work and socializing

21st Century Leaders

Future Skils

March 2021

Learn the 21st century skills needed in work and develop soft skills to gain future success